/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038be380c817f0398fcd794"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-MBBS-colleges-in-karnataka?-",
    "answer" : "Rajesh Saagar, consultantUpdated 6 years ago · Author has 241 answers and 614.7K answer viewsWhich are the best MBBS colleges in karnataka? Rajesh Saagar",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:24:08.070Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best MBBS colleges in karnataka? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038be530c817f0398fcd7b1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "List of top 10 medical colleges in Bangalore 1) Vydehi Institute of Medical Sciences and Research Centre, Bangalore Address: 82 Near BMTC 18th Depot Nallurahalli, EPIP Zone, Whitefield, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560066 Phone: 080 2841 2956 Website: Vydehi Institute of Medical Sciences and Research Centre, Bangalore 2) Bangalore Medical College and Research Institute Address: Fort, Krishna Rajendra Rd, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560002 Phone: 080 2670 1529 Website: http://www.bmcri.org 3) St. John’s Medical College, Bangalore Address: Sarjapur Main Rd, Beside Bank Of Baroda, John Nagar, Koramangala, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560034 Phone: 080 4946 6029 Website: St. John's National Academy of Health Sciences 4) M.S Ramaiah Medical College, Bangalore Address: M S Ramaiah Nagar, Mathikere, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560054 Phone: Continue Reading List of top 10 medical colleges in Bangalore 1) Vydehi Institute of Medical Sciences and Research Centre, Bangalore Address: 82 Near BMTC 18th Depot Nallurahalli, EPIP Zone, Whitefield, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560066 Phone: 080 2841 2956 Website: Vydehi Institute of Medical Sciences and Research Centre, Bangalore 2) Bangalore Medical College and Research Institute Address: Fort, Krishna Rajendra Rd, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560002 Phone: 080 2670 1529 Website: http://www.bmcri.org 3) St. John’s Medical College, Bangalore Address: Sarjapur Main Rd, Beside Bank Of Baroda, John Nagar, Koramangala, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560034 Phone: 080 4946 6029 Website: St. John's National Academy of Health Sciences 4) M.S Ramaiah Medical College, Bangalore Address: M S Ramaiah Nagar, Mathikere, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560054 Phone: Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:24:35.899Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best MBBS college in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038be6e0c817f0398fcd89d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Mumbai-in-2020?-",
    "answer" : "List of Top MBBS Colleges in Mumbai Based on 2020 Ranking : Grant Medical College and Sir J. J Group of Hospitals Seth G S Medical College LokmanyaTilak Municipal Medical College Topiwala National Medical College K. J Somaiya Medical College& Research Center Terna Medical college MGM Medical College FY Patil University Mahatma Gandhi Mission Institute Of Health and Science Rajiv Gandhi Medical College Maharashtra University of Health Science GMERS Medical College",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:25:02.596Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best MBBS college in Mumbai in 2020? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038beb40c817f0398fcd9af"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-medical-university-for-MBBS-in-Kazakhstan?-",
    "answer" : "Hi, Well as many of you know Kazakhstan is the most preferred location for medical students. There are number of Universities in Kazakhstan but the best medical university preferred by most of the students is Asfendiyarov Kazakh National Medical University. It is the oldest medical university in Kazakhstan.  Here I will list some of the points and specialities of Kazakh National Medical University. Asfendiyarov National Medical University achieved the title of Kazakh National Medical University because of its best education system.KazNMU offers a number of medical courses under bachelor, master degrees and doctorate programs.KazNMU conducts training in 51 specialities.KazNMU keeps improving their healthcare through integration of medical technologies.KazNMU is recognized by-Medical council of InContinue Reading Hi, Well as many of you know Kazakhstan is the most preferred location for medical students. There are number of Universities in Kazakhstan but the best medical university preferred by most of the students is Asfendiyarov Kazakh National Medical University. It is the oldest medical university in Kazakhstan.  Here I will list some of the points and specialities of Kazakh National Medical University. Asfendiyarov National Medical University achieved the title of Kazakh National Medical University because of its best education system.KazNMU offers a number of medical courses under bachelor, master degrees and doctorate programs.KazNMU conducts training in 51 specialities.KazNMU keeps improving their healthcare through integration of medical technologies.KazNMU is recognized by-Medical council of InContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:26:12.213Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best medical university for MBBS in Kazakhstan? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bec70c817f0398fcd9bf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-names-of-the-best-MBBS-colleges-in-India-and-the-admission-process?-",
    "answer" : "For getting the complete list of colleges is available at www.mciindia.org (Official website of Medical Council of India)- Government medical colleges- Private medical colleges- Overseas MBBS universitieswebsite links is given for every colleges throughout the country. For e-Guide on MBBS admission, you may download the same at http://summerinternz.com/moksh16/mbbs-admission/ Kritika Pandey",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:26:31.644Z"),
    "question" : "What are the names of the best MBBS colleges in India and the admission process? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bedc0c817f0398fcd9d5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MBBS-university-in-China?-",
    "answer" : "Preethi Selvaraj China is already known for its lower packages MBBS medical course offering both for the Chinese and the international students, yet if you are seeking for the medical colleges which can offer you MBBS in the lowest package, then here we are suggesting you few names. JILIN UniversityJILIN is the well known medical university in China for its lowest MBBS packages offering. You can pursue MBBS from here at a very limited budget. NANJING Medical UniversityThis is the other medical university in China from where you can take up the MBBS program at the lowest package. HUAZHONG University of Science and TechnologyHUAZHONG is a famous medical university in China for the stream of medical and science. It offers the MBBS program at a very lower package in China. Advantages of Studying MBBS in China The c Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:26:52.059Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best MBBS university in China? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bf0e0c817f0398fcdad6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Russia-for-an-Indian?-",
    "answer" : "Hello best colleges with total fee packages (tuition fees,hostel,food,daily expenses) with 28 lakh package kazan state medical universitykazan federal universityOrenburg medical universityTver state medical universityBashkir state medical universitypackage under 28 lakh crimea federal medical universitysiberian state medical universityperm state medical universityMari state medical universityWhy Indian Students Should Get Their MBBS in Russia Russia is one of the most popular options for getting an MBBS abroad and has many different options of universities. Russia has many of the oldest and most respected universities in the world for studying medicine and provides students with unparalleled research training. Russia is a popular choice for many foreign students because of its great balance betw Continue Reading Hello best colleges with total fee packages (tuition fees,hostel,food,daily expenses) with 28 lakh package kazan state medical universitykazan federal universityOrenburg medical universityTver state medical universityBashkir state medical universitypackage under 28 lakh crimea federal medical universitysiberian state medical universityperm state medical universityMari state medical universityWhy Indian Students Should Get Their MBBS in Russia Russia is one of the most popular options for getting an MBBS abroad and has many different options of universities. Russia has many of the oldest and most respected universities in the world for studying medicine and provides students with unparalleled research training. Russia is a popular choice for many foreign students because of its great balance betw Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:27:42.740Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best MBBS college in Russia for an Indian? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bf220c817f0398fcdbc1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Dhaka?-",
    "answer" : "Hafsa Baig",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:28:02.777Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best MBBS college in Dhaka? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bf710c817f0398fcdce0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-you-convince-me-that-PMCH-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Bihar?-",
    "answer" : "Manindra Kumar, lives in Patna, Bihar, IndiaAnswered 3 years ago · Author has 98 answers and 175.4K answer viewsHow can you convince me that PMCH is the best MBBS college in Bihar? Manindra Kumar It's not easy for someone to answer this question on a public platform. As you have included this question in topic ‘ igims patna’, i think you want someone from igims only to answer. Pmch is a dream college for every medical aspirant, if he is from bihar. It is an old and established institution so no doubt it is a first choice medical college from bihar qouta. On the other side, igims patna has its own history. One of a kind, autonomous super specialty hospital of bihar. So, igims patna has a lot to achieve and it can be rightly said that it's on a right track so far. I may not convince you that pmch is the best, but i least let me tell you that it must be your first choice too. Reason- just one,it is an old and reputed institution. If you want different opinions then you can add this simil Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:29:21.022Z"),
    "question" : "How can you convince me that PMCH is the best MBBS college in Bihar? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bf830c817f0398fcdcf3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-we-select-the-best-MBBS-college?-",
    "answer" : "Shweta RaneAnswered October 26, 2020How can we select the best MBBS college? Shweta Rane",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:29:39.162Z"),
    "question" : "How can we select the best MBBS college? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bf950c817f0398fcdddb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-MBBS-colleges-in-India-for-being-admitted-into-after-achieving-more-than-500-marks-in-the-NEET?-",
    "answer" : "Yeah!! There are many possibilities of getting admission into good medical colleges with your NEET-UG score i.e. 590–600. I guess there will be difficulty in getting into reputed medical colleges with All India counseling conducted by MCC. But there is great possibility that you will get admission into your state's great medical colleges. This depends on your state counseling criteria. Because in states, there is 85% quota for that state's students.Which will help you in getting admission in your state's reputed Medical colleges. All the best!!😊",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:29:57.992Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best MBBS colleges in India for being admitted into after achieving more than 500 marks in the NEET? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bfbd0c817f0398fcddfb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Greater-Noida?-",
    "answer" : "Udit Vaish, MBBS Surgery & Medicine, School Of Medical Science And Research, Sharda University (2021)Answered 3 years agoHow is Sharda University, Greater Noida for an MBBS degree? Udit Vaish",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:30:37.361Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best MBBS college in Greater Noida? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bfd80c817f0398fcdeea"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-good-for-an-MBBS-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Eduvaarta Sip Ans :- Bachelor of Medicine and Bachelor of Surgery or in Latin - Medicinae Baccalaureus Baccalaureus Chirugiae (MBBS) is a 5.5 to 6 years bachelor degree for medical students. There are more than 450 colleges all over the country. Some of them are listed below: - GOVERNMENT - 1) AIIMS, New Delhi All India Institute of Medical Sciences (AIIMS) is top ranked government college in India. It is best known for charging subsidize tuition fees. AIIMS offers courses like - Bachelor of Optometry, Bachelor of Surgery, Bachelor of Medicine, MD/MS, M.D.S., Biochemistry, Anatomy, Physiology, Nursing etc. If you want to take admission in AIIMS you have to clear AIIMS Entrance Exam. There are only 70 seats available for medical students. 2) PGIMER, Chandigarh Post Graduate Institute of Medical Education and R Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:31:04.788Z"),
    "question" : "Which college is good for an MBBS in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038bff70c817f0398fcdf04"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-best-MBBS-colleges-in-Dehradun?-",
    "answer" : "In dehradun there are 4 colleges out of which one is government medical college and rest are private 1.Government medical college doon 2.Himalayan Institute Of Medical Sciences 3.Shri Guru Ram Rai Institute Of Medical And Health Sciences 4.Sridev Suman Subharti Medical College",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:31:35.081Z"),
    "question" : "What are some best MBBS colleges in Dehradun? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c0680c817f0398fce117"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-some-best-MBBS-colleges-in-foreign-countries-for-Indian-students?-",
    "answer" : "Top medical destinations in the world- Best Institutions: Harvard UniversityStanford UniversityJohns Hopkins UniversityUniversity of Californiaâ€”â€‹San FranciscoUniversity of Pennsylvania (Perelman)Washington University in St. LouisYale UniversityColumbia UniversityDuke UniversityUniversity of Chicago (Pritzker)Jiangsu UniversityCentral South UniversityZhengzhou UniversitySoutheast UniversityHuazhong University of Science and TechnologyTianjin Medical UniversityDalian Medical UniversityWuhan UniversityCapital Medical UniversityLomonosov Moscow State UniversityRussian State Medical University, MoscowVolgograd State Medical University,VolgogradKursk State Medical University, KurskKazan State Medical University, KAZANTver State Medical AcademyI.M. Sechenov Moscow Medical AcademyPeople’s Friendship University of Russia, MoscowNational Technical University of UkraineNational Pedagogical UniversityTaurida National UniversityOdessa I.I. Mechnikov National UniversityIvan Franko National University of LvivNational University of Life and Environmental Sciences of UkraineTaras Shevchenko National University of KyivNational University of Kyiv-Mohyla AcademyNational Mining UniversityKharkiv National UniversityUniversity of OxfordUniversity of CambridgeUCLImperial College LondonKings College LondonThe University of EdinburghThe University of ManchesterLondon School of Hygiene and Tropical MedicineQueen Mary University of LondonThe University of NottinghamUniversity of MelbourneThe University of SydneyThe University of New South WalesMonash UniversityThe University of QueenslandThe Australian National UniversityThe University of AdelaideThe University of WesternThe University of NewcastleThe University of WollongonRuprecht-Karls-UniversitÃ¤t HeidelbergLudwig Maximilian University of MunichHumboldt University of BerlinGeorg-August-UniversitÃ¤t GÃ¶ttingenTechnical University of MunichRWTH Aachen UniversityAlbert-Ludwigs-UniversitÃ¤t FreiburgKarlsruhe Institute of TechnologyHamburg UniversityUniversitÃ¤t Bonn",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:33:28.824Z"),
    "question" : "What are the some best MBBS colleges in foreign countries for Indian students? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c0a50c817f0398fce228"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-name-of-the-best-MBBS-college-in-UP?-",
    "answer" : "GS Medical College & Hospital is one of the best medical college for MBBS Course in up as compare to another private colleges. Why is the best? -Big Infrastructure -Big Library -Affordable fee structure -Latest Equipment -Experienced Faculty & Many more which is make it best. GS Medical College & Hospital",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:34:29.459Z"),
    "question" : "What is the name of the best MBBS college in UP? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c1800c817f0398fce640"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-university-for-an-MBBS-in-the-Philippines?-",
    "answer" : "Ryan FernandoAnswered 1 year agoWhich is the best university for an MBBS in the Philippines? Ryan Fernando Before suggesting which university is the best for MBBS in the Philippines, here are some insights on MBBS in the Philippines. Read this and decide if it is worth doing MBBS in the Philippines. 3 Main reasons why should not study MBBS in the Philippines No Student Visa All the students get only a tourist visa and which need to be renewed for every 2 months with 10000 INR. so just calculate the expenses that are to be spent for your next 4-6 years… You can not directly pursue your MBBS The student has to get enrolled in an 18 month long pre-medical course. This is a BS- Program. Only after passing this BS exam you have to appear for NMAT exam and be in the 40 percentile minimum to be eligible for joining MD program which is actually the undergraduate program in medicine in the Philippines. Very l Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:38:08.917Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best university for an MBBS in the Philippines? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c1950c817f0398fce652"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-get-the-best-MBBS-seat-in-Maharashtra?-",
    "answer" : "Answering purely on basis of wat d students going fir MBA tell me Govt medical colleges r most preferred like Bombay hospital, Sion hospital, KEM, Nair, JJ etc bcoz u get real experience of handling actual cases by docs who r veteran in their field not just in theory but also for dealing with patients irresp of huge volumes n many disorders n diseases n combinations of these etc Ramanan Duraiswami",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:38:29.724Z"),
    "question" : "How can I get the best MBBS seat in Maharashtra? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c1ae0c817f0398fce66c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Tamil-Nadu-with-a-low-fee-structure-in-the-B-category?-",
    "answer" : "Muhammed Aslam Aslam, Studies MBBS at Tirunelveli Medical College.Answered 7 months agoWhat is the fee structure for an MBBS in Tamil Nadu Government Medical College? Muhammed Aslam Aslam Its Rs.15,000 in first yr and while joining the college you have to give an additional Rs. 10,000 as saftey deposit which you will get back after completing the course.Then its less than Rs 15,000 in the second yr (dont remember the exact figures)and third yr its Rs7000 and similar fee in final year. P.S The hostel fee and mess bill is not included which in my college (Tirunelveli Medical College) is around Rs 5000 per month and every year there is university exam fee which is 12,000 in first years and close to Rs 20000 in final year. So we can average acedamic cost of Rs 50000 per year. Without including mess billl. But you have Rs 20,000 per month as stipend that you get during CRRI period(House Surgeon intership ). So that evens things out when you finish your course.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:38:54.379Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best MBBS college in Tamil Nadu with a low fee structure in the B category? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c1eb0c817f0398fce77d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-type-of-medical-college-should-one-select-for-pursuing-an-MBBS?-",
    "answer" : "Hritik Taletiya Criteria for selection of Medical College 1. College Infrastructure. 2. Internal PG (as in AIIMS, VMMC & IMS-BHU) 3. Hospital Infrastructure. 4. Average number of patients visiting the OPD per day. 5. City (Delhi = Mumbai > State Capital > Cities >Town 6. Number of State P.G. seats (UG:PG ratio) 7. Bond for rural posting (in Maharashtra) 8. Faculty 9..Past academic record 10. Hostel facilities (you are going to spend the most unforgettable 5 and 1/2 years of your life here!!!) 11. Ragging scenario – yes it is still prevalent in many colleges in UP and Bihar; but it’s fun in rest of the colleges. 12. Fees (lowest in AIIMS, MAMC, LHMC & UCMS) 13. Recreation Facilities – sports, culture, literature – AIIMS and AFMC are the colleges where you would get ample opportunity to groom your interests and passion.  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:39:55.620Z"),
    "question" : "What type of medical college should one select for pursuing an MBBS? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c2110c817f0398fce873"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-MBBS-college-admission-consultants-in-Tamil-Nadu?-",
    "answer" : "NONE. NONE. U must clear NEET exam. Or ready to pay RS 5 million minimum to get management quota.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:40:33.535Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best MBBS college admission consultants in Tamil Nadu? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c23d0c817f0398fce973"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-was-your-best-MBBS-medical-college-memory?-",
    "answer" : "Not exactly the best but one of the best. You see I'm in 2nd year yet and a lot of great experiences await in future. Disclaimer: ⚠️this content may appear gross to few⚠️ This happened like around 7 months ago. Our batch was posted in surgery department. That day was a memorable one because we saw a case of cellulitis for the first time. It looked gross with muscles and a part of bone being visible too. One of my friend assisted the staff nurse in the dressing of that patient. I was eager to help but also hesitant at the same time because believe me or not the sight was pretty awful. After that , there came in a patient with his 3rd toe bandaged. He was quite elderly and was assisted by a younger guy( his son probably). At first instance i felt like , that's pretty easy peasy. The usual algori Continue Reading Not exactly the best but one of the best. You see I'm in 2nd year yet and a lot of great experiences await in future. Disclaimer: ⚠️this content may appear gross to few⚠️ This happened like around 7 months ago. Our batch was posted in surgery department. That day was a memorable one because we saw a case of cellulitis for the first time. It looked gross with muscles and a part of bone being visible too. One of my friend assisted the staff nurse in the dressing of that patient. I was eager to help but also hesitant at the same time because believe me or not the sight was pretty awful. After that , there came in a patient with his 3rd toe bandaged. He was quite elderly and was assisted by a younger guy( his son probably). At first instance i felt like , that's pretty easy peasy. The usual algori Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:41:17.159Z"),
    "question" : "What was your best MBBS medical college memory? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c2dd0c817f0398fcec84"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-canada-the-best-place-to-do-MBBS?-",
    "answer" : "To begin with, the medical schools in Canada do not offer the MBBS degree. Canadian medical schools are accredited by Liaison Committee on Medical Education (LCME). These medical schools, therefore, follow the US model that require medical schools applicants to complete a baccalaureate degree (if not in a combined BS-MD program). Canadian medical students complete 4 years of education and graduate with the MD (Doctor of Medicine) degree. Some medical schools also offer the MD CM degree (where CM is Master of Surgery). While it is arguably that the best medical schools are among those in the United States, the Canadian medical schools are quite competitive. Being LCME-accredited, graduates of Canadian medical schools are not considered as foreign medical graduates when applying for residency  Continue Reading To begin with, the medical schools in Canada do not offer the MBBS degree. Canadian medical schools are accredited by Liaison Committee on Medical Education (LCME). These medical schools, therefore, follow the US model that require medical schools applicants to complete a baccalaureate degree (if not in a combined BS-MD program). Canadian medical students complete 4 years of education and graduate with the MD (Doctor of Medicine) degree. Some medical schools also offer the MD CM degree (where CM is Master of Surgery). While it is arguably that the best medical schools are among those in the United States, the Canadian medical schools are quite competitive. Being LCME-accredited, graduates of Canadian medical schools are not considered as foreign medical graduates when applying for residency  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:43:57.746Z"),
    "question" : "Is canada the best place to do MBBS? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c3670c817f0398fceea9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-MBA-colleges-in-India-in-2020?-",
    "answer" : "Akanksha Nagar, PGDM  Retail, Birla Institute of Management TechnologyUpdated November 20, 2020What are the top MBA colleges in India in 2020? Akanksha Nagar",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:46:15.538Z"),
    "question" : "What are the top MBA colleges in India in 2020? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c37b0c817f0398fceebd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-MBBS-college-in-Kerala?-",
    "answer" : "1.Trivandrum 2.Calicut 3.kottayam 4.thrissur 5.alappuzha 6.kollam 7.kalamaserry (cochin ) 8and 9.Palakkad=Manjeri 10.amala, thrissur 11.jubilee mission, thrissur 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:46:35.971Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best MBBS college in Kerala? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c3c70c817f0398fcefd9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-currently-the-best-MBBS-medical-college-in-West-Bengal?-",
    "answer" : "Aishik Kundu Top 5 list of best MBBS Colleges in West Bengal - Medical College, Kolkata - It has always been the best medical college in West Bengal. Though, the national rankings place it at 3rd position among the medical colleges in West Bengal, it has traditionally been a very good college & has produced great doctors in the past.Nilratan Sirkar (NRS) Medical College - another very good college. National rankings place it 2nd.R. G. Kar Medical College - it is ranked as the best medical college in West Bengal according to national rankings.Institute of Post Graduate Medical Education & Research (IPGMER)Calcutta National Medical CollegeThese are the top 5 best medical colleges in West Bengal. All are located in Kolkata. The idea of ‘the best college’ is debatable. All the 5 are very good colleges.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:47:51.759Z"),
    "question" : "Which is currently the best MBBS medical college in West Bengal? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c3da0c817f0398fcf0c0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-one-is-best-college-for-MBBS-in-Russia-with-sure-success?-",
    "answer" : "Abha Chaterjee Greetings to whoever is reading this answer right now. I am an Indian student pursuing my MBBS from Russia at Crimea Federal University which is one of the top ranked and oldest Universities of Russia. So first of all, I will brief you about my University only. Language of instruction during our lectures is purely English. Though we are supposed to learn Russian language so as to have a better interaction with the patients and locals. Quality of education here is really well and the professors here are highly experienced and really supportive towards the students. Speaking of climate, yes it gets a little bit harsh during the winters. Otherwise, it’s very much fine. The University is located in a secure region and you’re not allowed to exit the campus premise after the stipulated hours at nig Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:48:10.245Z"),
    "question" : "Which one is best college for MBBS in Russia with sure success? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c4270c817f0398fcf1d9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-best-private-MBBS-college-in-Gujarat?-",
    "answer" : "Dhirubhai Ambani Institute of Information and Communication Technology, GandhinagarPandit Deendayal Petroleum University, GandhinagarCharotar University of Science and Technology, PetladAdani Institute of Infrastructure Engineering, AhmedabadGH Patel College of Engineering and Technology, AnandBirla Vishvakarma Mahavidyalaya, AnandAD Patel Institute of Technology, Anandget Admission Guidance in Pvt. Colleges for MBBS/BDS Contact Our Help deak or whatsapp 9538883335 Umang Kardani",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:49:27.926Z"),
    "question" : "Which is best private MBBS college in Gujarat? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c4a70c817f0398fcf3f5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-private-MBBS-college-in-UP?-",
    "answer" : "In Uttar Pradesh there are about 17 private medical colleges which are providing the MBBS degree after the expenditure of at least 70,00,000( 70 lacs) Indian national rupee as college fee plus hostel charge. I can provide you the fee list posted by the government of Uttar Pradesh on their website. Now come to your question. On the basis of the trend followed by the students in previous years of selecting the seat in private medical college the best college comes out to be is SRMS BAREILLY. Students with high all India Rank like 17839 are taking admission in this college here I am going to provide you the allotment list of 2017. All top rankers who doesn't make their seat in government medical college they preferred the SRMS BAREILLY. And all other medical college are also good so make your c Continue Reading In Uttar Pradesh there are about 17 private medical colleges which are providing the MBBS degree after the expenditure of at least 70,00,000( 70 lacs) Indian national rupee as college fee plus hostel charge. I can provide you the fee list posted by the government of Uttar Pradesh on their website. Now come to your question. On the basis of the trend followed by the students in previous years of selecting the seat in private medical college the best college comes out to be is SRMS BAREILLY. Students with high all India Rank like 17839 are taking admission in this college here I am going to provide you the allotment list of 2017. All top rankers who doesn't make their seat in government medical college they preferred the SRMS BAREILLY. And all other medical college are also good so make your c Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:51:35.255Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best private MBBS college in UP? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c4f40c817f0398fcf512"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-or-top-government-MBBS-college-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "The all time favourite for every medical aspirants & of course the best among the top colleges of India is AIIMS,Delhi. Having done your mbbs from this college is like a dream come true, it's like a passport for the doctors. After all such is the power of reputated institution. Aastha Vijay",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:52:52.558Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best or top government MBBS college in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c51d0c817f0398fcf60c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-private-MBBS-college-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "I don't know about others but kamineni (lb nagar) is hell! They just eat your money .They charge you for everything and provide you nothing! they are very greedy and illogical.They don't have any sports facility no ground ! No AC ! No library books! It's jail where you pay and they enjoy and grow with your money! Money eaters!!! 9",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:53:33.636Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best private MBBS college in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c5a70c817f0398fcf83d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-in-India-has-the-lowest-fee-structure-for-MBBS-courses?-",
    "answer" : "first of all, keep in mind that due to political intereferences by politicians, in govt and pvt mb bs colleges, there are admission restrictions. state colleges are bound by state domicile restrictions and state neet list many medical colleges like all india institute of medical sciences have their own entrance tests. there are 15% reservations for central quotas, minority colleges like christian medical college, take sponsored candidates. there are reservations for sc/st/ obcs pvt medical colleges have management quotas least fees are for state colleges as they receive grants from state- but are based on state domicile and ranking in neet from state .",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:55:51.160Z"),
    "question" : "Which college in India has the lowest fee structure for MBBS courses? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c5b90c817f0398fcf921"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-private-MBBS-colleges-in-Karnataka?-",
    "answer" : "Best private medical colleges in karnataka are 1.kasturba medical college - Manipal 2. Kasturba medical college - Mangalore 3. MS Ramaiah medical college - Bangalore 4. Father muller medical college - Mangalore 5. Vydehi institute of medical sciences - Bangalore 6. JNMC - BELGIUM 7. JSS medical college - Mysore 8. KIMS - Bangalore Karthik Dammur",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:56:09.478Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best private MBBS colleges in Karnataka? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c5f10c817f0398fcfa2d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-MBBS-college-is-the-best-in-Nepal-for-Indians?-",
    "answer" : "Dinesh Singh Nepal is a preferred location, especially for Indian students owing to a number of reasons. The quality education provided by these institutes, competitive fee structure, and less complicated documentation are among few reasons, for Indian students choosing this country for higher education. Moreover the food habits, culture and lifestyle is matched to a great deal with that of India. Unlike other countries, you do not require any Visa to study in this country. Many of the colleges are approved by the Medical Council of India and even curriculum of MBBS course is similar to that followed in Indian counterparts. Being an English and Hindi speaking region, Indian students find it easy to communicate with the people of this country. Many universities and colleges of the country are approved by  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:57:05.139Z"),
    "question" : "Which MBBS college is the best in Nepal for Indians? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}


/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c67d0c817f0398fcfc5b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-colleges-in-Nepal-offer-an-MBBS-for-Indians?-",
    "answer" : "Many universities and colleges of the country are approved by MCI. Few reputed medical institutes are Kathmandu University, Tribhuvan University, Patan Academy of Health Sciences and B.P Koirala Institute of Health Sciences. These universities have different medical colleges under them that provide MBBS course to students. Based on the merit, these universities select students for medical courses. Few colleges also provide scholarships to students. The best colleges in Nepal for MBBS is B. P. Koirala Institute of Heath Sciences Institute of Medicine Kathmandu University School of Medical science Nepalese Army Institute of health sciences Patan Academy of Health Sciences Kathmandu Medical College",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T09:59:25.426Z"),
    "question" : "Which colleges in Nepal offer an MBBS for Indians? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c6df0c817f0398fcfe63"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-cheapest-private-medical-college-for-MBBS?-",
    "answer" : "Rahul Valath IT IS POSSIBLE ONLY IN THE PARALLEL UNIVERSE :p jokes apart, coming to your question . It is a myth if you are considering private medical college and that too with low fee.. though i don’t know what is low fees according to you it’s different for different people.The lowest fees is in karanataka i guess 5lakhs per year and its really tough for a non karantaka student to get there as compared to other state, because there is very small amount of seats reserved for non karnataka applicants , ad due to low fees almost all the 5lakh per year seats get filled in the 1st counselling only. If you are from karnataka or have a domiile of karnataka.I would say it would be easy for you secure a seat there. kerala too has very low fees same approx 4–5 lakhs but they increased the fees last year i gues Continue Reading IT IS POSSIBLE ONLY IN THE PARALLEL UNIVERSE :p jokes apart, coming to your question . It is a myth if you are considering private medical college and that too with low fee.. though i don’t know what is low fees according to you it’s different for different people.The lowest fees is in karanataka i guess 5lakhs per year and its really tough for a non karantaka student to get there as compared to other state, because there is very small amount of seats reserved for non karnataka applicants , ad due to low fees almost all the 5lakh per year seats get filled in the 1st counselling only. If you are from karnataka or have a domiile of karnataka.I would say it would be easy for you secure a seat there. kerala too has very low fees same approx 4–5 lakhs but they increased the fees last year i gues Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T10:01:03.394Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the cheapest private medical college for MBBS? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c6ef0c817f0398fcfe74"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-way-to-get-admission-in-a-government-MBBS-college?-",
    "answer" : "Sonali Shehnaz  There is no best way to get admission in a Govt. College for MBBS easily.. You can appear for NEET exam first score almost 600+ marks out of 720 to getting admission in any govt. College.. So study well.. Best of luck..",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T10:01:19.787Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best way to get admission in a government MBBS college? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6038c7160c817f0398fcff6f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-reputed-MBA-colleges-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Suprabha Singh The executives or a MBA is the most famous course among the understudies and experts. 6 out of 10 experts try to seek after a MBA in the wake of finishing their graduation. Some like to increase some understanding and give a lift to their vocation. Advantages of seeking after a MBA 1. It will offer you the chance to get set in the top organizations in India just as abroad. 2. MBA is a necessity for the situation of the director in the greater part of the organizations. 3. At the point when you seek after your MBA from first rate universities, you are with a group of top think-big haulers. This gives you the likelihood to cooperate in future and construct your group. Who ought not seek after a MBA 1. On the off chance that you are somebody who isn't excellent with mathematical abilities, and odds Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-26T10:01:58.715Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best reputed MBA colleges in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

